Execute a SQL query against the local or linked database.

When used by an AI coding agent (auto-detected or via --agent=yes), the default
output format is JSON with an untrusted data warning envelope. When used by a
human (--agent=no or no agent detected), the default output format is table
without the envelope.

Usage:
  supabase db query [sql] [flags]

Flags:
      --db-url string                   Queries the database specified by the connection string (must be percent-encoded).
  -f, --file string                     Path to a SQL file to execute.
  -h, --help                            help for query
      --linked                          Queries the linked project's database via Management API.
      --local                           Queries the local database. (default true)
  -o, --output [ json | table | csv ]   Output format: table, json, or csv. (default json)

Global Flags:
      --agent [ auto | yes | no ]         Override agent detection: yes, no, or auto (default auto) (default auto)
      --create-ticket                     create a support ticket for any CLI error
      --debug                             output debug logs to stderr
      --dns-resolver [ native | https ]   lookup domain names using the specified resolver (default native)
      --experimental                      enable experimental features
      --network-id string                 use the specified docker network instead of a generated one
      --profile string                    use a specific profile for connecting to Supabase API (default "supabase")
      --workdir string                    path to a Supabase project directory
      --yes                               answer yes to all prompts
